♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return
to The Autistic Postman Always
Rings Four Hundred Times.
So is everybody excited
for Father's Day on Sunday?
Oh, yeah,
that's right.
I always try to avoid
Father's Day now.
Every year, I used to take
my dad to the horse track.
Now we just go rooting around
for bargains at the mall.
Oh, this is darling, isn't it?
Uh-huh.
Glenn, do you think you'd see
my bra through this blouse?
Uh, I don't know.
Is it too sheer?
I don't know what that means.
Glenn? Do you think
it's too sheer?
I said I don't know!
Hey, Joe, you know,
come to think of it,
I've met
Cleveland's dad,
and my dog slept
with Quagmire's dad,
but I don't know anything
about your dad.
Yeah, is he
still with us,
or is he living in Heaven
with Jesus Christ?
Ugh, save that
for your black friends.
Eh, my dad's out
there somewhere,
but I haven't spoken
to him in years.
What?! Really?!
Sorry, Cleveland,
that was mean of me.
I already forgave you.
But, Joe, why haven't you
seen your dad?
Well, he's a good guy,
but we just drifted apart.
It's no big deal.
It's a very big deal.
My dad's a stinking drunk
who lives in Ireland,
but you got
a perfectly good dad.
You can't waste that.
You gotta call him up
for Father's Day.
Peter, I don't even know
where he is.
Who's ready for another beer?
Hey, Cleveland, weren't you
supposed to buy the next round?
That's a shame Joe
never sees his dad.
I know.
Hey, you know what?
Joe's our friend.
He should be with his dad
on Father's Day,
and we're gonna
track him down.
Yeah, that's a
good idea, Peter.
Well, I like
helping people out.
That's why I was such a good
break-up rodeo clown.
I'm just gonna go
ahead and tell you.
I've been sleeping
with your sister.
What?!
Hey, now! Hey, now!
Over here! Over here!
Over here! Hey, now!
Hey, now! Over here!
Over here!
Hey, now! Hey, now!
Over here! Over here!
Oh, and now that
I'm inside the barrel,
he gave you
and your sister HPV.
Hey, want to see
something?
Check out how hot
my last patient was.
Oh.
They look fake.
Yeah, who cares?
Okay, according
to this projection,
Stewie's adult height
will be five-foot-one.
What?!
Five-foot-one?!
Wow, Dr. Hartman,
that's really short.
I mean, I suppose it's fine
if he's gonna die at 14.
Is-is there anything
on there about that?
Well, we learned
in medical school
that the short ones
do go faster,
'cause they smell more farts
than the rest of us.
This is terrible!
I can't be short!
I'll be an outcast, like Rudolph
the Uncircumcised Reindeer.
Look, Rudolph, it's
not me, all right?
It's Dasher, he's
been complaining,
and he is the one who has
to look at it all night.
I don't know.
Mrs. Claus says
it'll decrease my sensitivity.
I-I'm sorry, why are you
talking to my wife about this?
Okay, you guys,
it's all set.
I found Joe's dad
on the Internet,
and he just e-mailed me
to say he's coming tomorrow.
All right, great, but remember,
this is a surprise for Joe.
Why are you
looking at me?
Because you're terrible
at keeping secrets.
No, I'm not;
I'm great at it.
Like when I was
an OB/GYN.
Well, I got the results
of your ultrasound,
and I got some
news for you.
Wait, wait, wait--
We don't want to know
if it's a boy or a girl.
Oh, okay.
Well, it's
not breathing.
Hey, guys.
Uh, uh, so, Joe,
big day tomorrow, eh?
Father's Day.
Gonna be home all day,
especially at 11:30 a.m.?
Peter.
What? I didn't say
anything about his dad.
My dad?
What about my dad?
Well, now that Quagmire ruined
the surprise, we found your dad!
You what?!
That's right.
He's coming tomorrow,
for Father's Day.
You shouldn't have
done that, Peter.
My father's not gonna
be happy to see me.
Sure he will.
Just get him one of them
Father's Day cards
what plays a song.
"Dad to the Bone."
"I'm Dad."
Pretty much anything with
"bad," you turn it to "dad."
Wait, w-why wouldn't
your dad be happy?
What, is he a jerk
or something?
No, it's just that
ever since I was a little kid,
he was constantly making
fun of handicapped people.
Really?
Yeah, my whole life,
my-my dad would ridicule
anyone in a wheelchair.
It was all,
"Hey, spaghetti legs!"
And, "Hey, rigatoni legs!"
And, uh, "Hey,
angel-hair legs!"
He was a sales manager
at Ronzoni.
Wow, then it must have been
hard for him to accept
when you were
paralyzed.
That's just it.
My dad doesn't know
I'm handicapped.
I never told him.
I never...
I never told him!
Ah, Joe, don't cry.
It's gonna make me cry.
I cry like Snoopy.
I can't believe you invited
my father without telling me.
You guys got to get
in touch with him
and tell him
not to come.
It's too late, Joe,
he's already on his way.
He is?
Yeah, we got him
tickets on Kayak.
It is a nightmare
itinerary.
It was, like, 80 bucks,
but he has four stops.
Two of them are
in Houston.
What am I gonna do?
My dad has no idea
I'm paralyzed.
Well, there's only
one thing we can do.
We'll just figure out a way
to hide your handicap
from your dad.
Hide the fact
that I can't walk?
Peter, that'll
never work.
It's worth a try.
Come on, Joe,
don't be so negative.
You're like a Boston
fortune cookie.
"I don't know, numbnuts.
Maybe buy a garage and fill it
with hockey equipment."
Huh.
Well, let's see
what my lucky numbers are.
"Screw you, math dick."
Well, that wasn't
very helpful at all.
Here you go, Stewie.
I know clothes shopping
always cheers you up.
I can't believe I'm only
going to be five-foot-one.
Aw, come on, look
at the bright side.
You'll be in the front row
of every class picture.
Holding that little plaque.
You suck.
Why don't you go drink out
of the fountain?
I'll text you
when I'm done.
I know you're
trying to be rude,
but I am gonna do that,
because I find it enjoyable.
Excuse me, I was
looking at this.
Sorry, I've made a decision
to go for that shirt,
and when that happens,
it is on.
Full throttle, man. Pow!
Wow, you're an energetic
little fellow.
I guess your mommy lets
you drink coffee, huh?
Whoa, whoa, I-I don't put
stimulants in my body.
You know something?
You kind of remind me
of Tom Cruise.
Boom.
You-you got me, man.
Wow,
Tom Cruise.
You look, um...
bigger in the movies.
Wh-What are you doing here?
Oh, I get all my clothes from
out-of-the-way toddler stores.
Ooh, uh, you want
an animal cracker?
Sure, you got
a lion in there?
Oh, no,
I eat those first.
I believe eating
the lions gives me power.
Yeah, I hear you believe
in a lot of crazy stuff.
What'd you get there?
A giraffe?
Yeah.
Good, good.
It's good for eyesight.
Well, you're certainly upbeat.
Let me ask you,
doesn't it bother you
being an adult man
who's that short?
'Cause the doctor says
that's where I'm headed.
Oh, no way, man.
The middle of the word
"short" is "or."
"Or" gives you a choice.
And I choose not to be short.
Wow, you need a road map
for that one.
Hey, hey,
I'll tell you what.
You spend the day with me,
you'll see how great
it is to be short.
You'll feel like
you're discovering a new world.
And you know what's in
the middle of the word "world"?
Um... "or"?
Yes!
The dots have appeared, man,
let's connect them!
You're... you're a weirdo,
but let's do this.
All right, check
it out, Bonnie.
This is how we're
gonna fool Joe's dad.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, looks
real, right?
I put this pair of pants
on the front legs of this horse
and strapped Joe
to the front
with his legs tied
behind the horse's neck.
And then we put Cinnamon's head
up the back of Joe's shirt
and simply hid the rest of the
horse behind this curtain.
His breath is very
moist, Peter.
And to induce movement, I'm
gonna snap the horse's balls
with this dampened
kitchen towel.
Aah! Oh, my God!
Holy crap, he's
out of control!
Does it look real?
Plan B! an B!
Peter, I'm
raid this is hopeless.
What, I don't know
what else to do.
I mean, we're not
gonna come up
with something better
than the horse.
Yeah, I guess you're just
gonna have to tell your dad
about your handicap.
I can't do that.
If you guys were in my shoes,
you'd understand.
Wait a minute, that's it!
I will get in your shoes.
I'll just pretend to be you.
I mean, your dad ain't
seen you in years.
He won't know
the difference.
What? That's crazy.
Boy, that was a close call.
Is some of this room cold?
All right, Peter,
almost done.
Huh? Huh?
Eh, kind of.
Yeah.
I don't care.
Peter, I don't
know about this.
It seems like
a bad idea.
Look, Lois, Joe is one
of my best friends, all right?
I'm only doing this
to help him.
Besides, wait till you hear
my "Joe" voice.
Uh, God, I hate
being stuck in this chair.
No, Peter,
that fights it.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Mr. Big Stuff ♪
♪ Who do you think you are? ♪
♪ You're never gonna
get my love ♪
♪ Now because you wear ♪
♪ All those fancy clothes ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ And have a big fine car ♪
♪ Oh, yes, you do now ♪
♪ Do you think I can afford ♪
♪ To give you my love ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ You think you're higher
than every star above ♪
♪ Mr. Big Stuff ♪
♪ Who do you think you are? ♪
♪ You're never gonna
make me cry ♪
♪ Mr. Big Stuff ♪
♪ Tell me, tell me... ♪
That's Bud.
Are you ready, Peter?
I think so.
What do you think,
acting coach?
I think you will be
exemplary, Peter.
All good acting coaches
are insane old ladies.
Emote!
Hi, Bud.
Hi, Joe's dad.
Uh, I mean, uh, Dad.
Uh, Joe, I'm Joe;
you're my dad.
Joe?
Wow, I guess it really
has been a long time.
I barely recognize you.
Put on a little weight,
haven't you?
Well, I could say
the same for you.
Sometimes I don't
understand why people laugh.
All right, everyone in the car.
We got a Father's Day
dinner reservation.
Why is Mr. Swanson coming?
And why is he dressed like Dad?
I don't know, kids.
I stopped asking after your
father said he shot a horse.
Thanks for
the ride-along.
I liked when you sentenced those
two girls to kiss each other.
Yeah, all girls are lesbians
when you point a gun at 'em.
Boy, it's been great
spending time with you, son.
It's been great spending
time with you, too...
Dad.
Oh, this'll be fun.
Let's see how long it takes them
to get Gumby over there
into the car.
Yeah, that's our neighbor,
Peter Griffin.
That's the guy
who e-mailed me?
Huh, no wonder it was all caps
with tons of typos.
He's a water head, right?
Yeah, he's a mess.
Look at his ugly kids.
Pathetic.
Ugh, he's not fitting.
Just put some of him
in the back like skis.
Hey, Stewie.
What's up?
When you
say it like that,
you sound just
like Tom Cruise.
What?
Oh, yeah,
I've been hanging
with Tom Cruise.
You've been hanging out
with Tom Cruise?
Sure have.
We spent the whole
day together,
and he showed me
there's a lot of
advantages to being short.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
You're the last one
to get wet when it rains?
Well, yeah, that.
And you can chow
pie standing up.
We didn't do any of that,
but the point is,
I'm at peace
with being short.
Full throttle, man!
Pow!
Hello?
Oh, hi,
Dr. Hartman.
Mrs. Griffin,
I have some good news.
Turns out your son
is going to be normal height.
I read his chart wrong
yesterday.
Apparently, I have something
called "dislooxia"?
That was the doctor.
Apparently, Stewie's not
gonna be short after all.
What? Really?
That's wonderful news!
Oh, I'm so relieved
my child is spared
some heartache.
Now, come on, Brian, I guess
we should try to make it
over to Meg's
birthday party.
Could I have some bread
while I open my presents?
At this point,
we're gonna have to start
charging you
for the bread.
Hey, Stewie!
You want to check out
the go-kart
I used in Days of Thunder?
Yeah, listen, um...
I just found out I'm
actually going to be tall,
so I'm no longer comfortable
hanging out with someone
whose teeth are bigger
than their fingers.
What?
That's...
that's barely true.
Yeah, so...
see you later.
You are making a big mistake,
Stewie!
Nobody walks away
from Tiny Tom Cruise!
Yeah, except for
all three of your wives.
Okay, I'm
shutting this now.
Okay, so... bye!
So now, since I switched
to disposable catheters,
I no longer have those beet-red
infections in my urethra.
Oh, no.
I hope it's not genetic.
Chris, he's
not our dad.
I can't keep up with this ruse.
Hey, everybody!
Peter, finally,
you're home.
How's it going over there
with my dad?
Awesome. He fell for
the whole thing.
In fact, we've been
having a great time!
Wow, that's
terrific, Peter!
You'll only have to pull it
off for a few more hours.
Then he'll be on a plane
tomorrow and I can go home.
Oh, that's
the other good news.
Bud's not leaving!
I told him he can move in
with me and Bonnie.
What?!
Peter, this is crazy!
Na it's gonna
work out fine.
Oh, and remember, Joe,
if Lois is feeling
frisky at night,
it's index finger
around and clockwise.
And just keep
doing that to yourself
until you're good to go.
Peter, this is ridiculous.
You can't live in my house
with my dad and my family!
Your dad got me
super clean in the tub.
Joe's right,
this is idiotic.
What are you thinking?
I'll tell you what I'm thinking.
I'm thinking that
I've had two dads
and neither one cared for me
as much as Bud does.
Peter, I've had
enough of this!
You can't just
take my dad!
Well, he's right
next door.
Nothing's stopping you
from going over there
and telling him the truth:
that his son is a paraplegic
who's stuck in a wheelchair.
You know I
can't do that.
Ah, suit yourself.
But I gotta go.
Me and Bud are
having a blast.
I'm sorry, Joe.
A-Are you okay?
Not really.
I'll be honest,
Lois, this hurts.
Hurts like the Dickens.
I've finished
my latest novel.
Splendid, Charles!
What is it called?
Oliver Nipple-Twist.
Ow!
Oh, Charles, you bastard!
Yeah! The Dickens!
It hurts like the me!
So, anyone going to
the gerbil's funeral on Friday?
Okay, kids!
Everyone in a circle
for parachute time.
Oh, goodie,
I love parachute time!
Whee!
What the hell?
That kid looked like
Tiny Tom Cruise.
Whee!
Huh.
Must've been my imagination.
Aah!
If you think
you're getting away from me,
you've got a crazy laugh
coming, friend.
Aah!
Hey, what are you doing home
so early?
He's following me, Brian!
Who's following you?
Tom Cruise!
I spend one afternoon
with the guy,
and it's like I signed
an eight-year contract
to show up at events with him
and let him fake-father a child.
Stewie, I would think Tom Cruise
has better things to do
than follow you around.
Oh, really?
Well, explain that!
You know, it's times
like this where I think,
if I didn't talk and
you were a normal baby,
we wouldn't have
any of these problems.
You gotta help me
get rid of him, Brian!
He's creepier
than that guy at the gym
who just does karate
in the mirror.
It's me.
The guy's me.
I'm a gym karate creep.
I'm pretty good, too.
But relax.
If I wanted you dead,
you'd be dead.
Hey, Dad, what do you
say we go play catch?
And throw me
some divers.
I want to get grass stains
on my school slacks.
What?
You're a grown man.
I know, it's just so
great having a dad.
Well, it's nice having
reconnected with you, too.
All right, let's do it.
Oh, for God's sake.
See, a guy like that
should just stay inside
so we don't have
to look at him.
Joe, go over there
and tell him to get
back in his house.
Don't worry, I'll
take care of it.
Joe, you gotta go inside.
You're upsetting my dad.
Your dad?
That's right!
He loves me
in a way that...
Aw, you guys had pizza?
Screw you, Peter!
You know what? This is over!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Not a chance.
I like your house better.
I got nothing to hold onto
when I poop at home.
You have no idea how many shower
curtains I've ripped down.
Now get inside.
No, I'm not
gonna do that.
Oh, yes, you are!
Get away from me,
you son of a bitch!
What the hell?
Joe, don't take that
from him!
How do you like that?
You're getting
your ass kicked by a cripple!
A helpless,
spaghetti-legged cripple!
What are you doing?
You're my son!
You can't let yourself
get beat up
by a guy
in a wheelchair!
Your son is a guy
in a wheelchair.
What are you talking about?
Yes.
Yes, Dad.
It's me.
Joe!
What the hell
happened to you?
I was shot in
the line of duty.
"Line of duty."
So, this is why you haven't
called me in all these years?
How could I, Dad?
You always made fun
of handicapped people.
The only thing I never
understood was... why?
I don't know.
I guess I could
never stand the thought
of something like that
happening to me.
Or even worse, to someone
that I care about.
One time, my legs fell
asleep on the toilet.
I had to crawl
into the living room
and interrupt
Lois's book club.
That was one of the shower
curtains I ripped down.
And I suppose, deep down,
I was afraid.
Afraid that, if it did happen,
I wouldn't be strong enough
to handle it.
Well, Dad, I can tell you
from experience
it's only when
your worst fears come true
that you get to find out
how strong you really are.
Then I guess I've got
some learning to do.
I love you, son.
I love you, too, Dad.
Hey, Joe, uh,
just one question:
why do you have all those
Wizard of Oz plates?
Because if I finish
my vegetables,
I get to see
the Yellow Brick Road.
All right,
you sold me.
All right, Brian,
Tiny Tom Cruise
is somewhere close.
I can sense
his manic energy.
You remember the plan?
Yup, I got it.
Help, help!
My dog got off his leash!
Is there anyone
who can do a pumpy-arm run?
Running, running, running,
running, running, running, run!
Hey, Stewie. I'm here to help
you for the next billion years.
All right, good to know.
Anyway, my dog ran
around those bushes.
I am on it!
Gotcha!
All right,
off to Zappos with him.
You sure this
is gonna work?
Oh, yeah.
They'll accept any returns.
We don't even
have to pay postage.
Hello, friend.
Your life...
is about to change.
Hey, Tom. It's been
a couple weeks.
Hey, listen, Joe, I'm sorry
I treated you like such a jerk.
Well, that's okay, Peter.
In fact, I got to say, it
was a nice thing you did.
I'm glad I reconnected with
my dad after all these years.
Ah, it was my pleasure.
There's no more important
relationship than...
I'm sorry, Cleveland,
what the hell
is that
Toronto Raptors hat?
It was my
Father's Day present.
I hate it.
I'm just gonna
wear it for a week
then say
I lost it.
Anyway, thanks for
helping me, Peter.
Yeah, it all
worked out great, Joe.
Except I am still missing
that one pair of pants.
Excuse me,
are those Bugle Boy jeans?
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru